We will go far, we will go through the
lion's dance completely, right to the
end. Prepare yourselves for
meditation. Turn off your phone.
Now test it. Here we go.
Comfortable posture,
a posture in which you do
n't have to move for a while. Relax the distractions
and try to keep them relaxed.
During meditation, relax
the corners of your mouth, your shoulders a
little further back, which means your hands
slide
back a little on your thighs. Your
fingers are relaxed. Gentle smile.
Then slowly concentrate on your
breath and a 10/10 slow exhalation.
And then we put ourselves in the
state of desire. You
can concentrate on the air conditioner
and the noises in the room
and outside.
Now compare the noise with
your heartbeat.
Try to hear the air conditioner and
your heartbeat at the same time.
Then leave the air conditioner behind
and immerse yourself completely in the heartbeat.
A first stage of the form realm.
And then decide
to go into the heartbeat instead of
watching it.
No noticeable...  Heartbeat
no longer checking the heartbeat milk
that in the middle of the heartbeat become
aware of the good posture
and notice what a relief
it is to completely lose yourself here
then we move on to the third stage of the
form realm
leave the feeling of pleasant stillness
behind you and enter a neutral
feeling mentally
the guardian in the mind very strong and
observes if there is any distraction
you are very very attentive if the
mind wanders and brings it back immediately
the body still feels very
pleasant so well aligned but the
mental feeling is neutral
the fourth form realm the fourth stage
in the area leave the pleasant feeling of the
body behind you
the body will
no longer perceive anything in the body of the
mind neutral feelings neutral
feelings and stays with one point on
which you concentrate
now the first stage of the formless realm
expand this one point in all
directions times further into the
infinite space
second stage of the formless realm
burdens the ceiling of space and only the  Mind
remains, mind now finally
expanded to infinitely many points,
and no awareness of space is present anymore. The
third stage of the formless realm
makes the decision to
let go of the awareness of mind and abide
in nothingness.
And for the fourth stage, decide
now:
I don't even want to bother thinking
about nothing anymore.
[Music]
That's a kind of darkness.
Thinking about nothing
is distraction.
[Music]
And I choose neither.
I will immerse myself in an even deeper stillness,
not holding onto my mind,
but also not bothering to hold onto it.
Now we go even further
into meditation on the majority.
Imagine your very own
heart teacher in your mind. Imagine
them sitting before you to receive
attention. Imagine with
their third eye that
they are looking at each other with uncanny
love radiating from their eyes.
And then think about where the
name comes from. Even the image you are
imagining right now, the one you are
placing before you, even this image comes
from a  Imagine a strange seed ripening
in your mind.
Now imagine this
seed opening, a small silver seed
in your mind. It opens, and
a small image of light emerges,
presenting itself to your own mind. You
see the face of
your llama and its eyes looking back at you.
Try to imagine this a few times,
three or four times, as
the image opens, this image emerges, this image
presents itself to your mind.
Now concentrate on this
silver seed in your mind.
Relax,
concentrate on the silver
seed,
and then let your mind
imagine how you planted this seed in
your past lives. Start
inventing the film of the seed that
now allows you to see the llama.
Relax, don't try so hard. What
images appear
from past lives?
If something interesting presents itself, like how
you might have planted this seed for
this life, then follow it
and make a
story out of it in your mind. Be creative,
rearrange all the images that seem to
appear randomly.
We'll do this now for the...  Next
five minutes and then we end the
meditation.
Perhaps you have done exactly these meditations in this life
and can now return to the face
of a teacher and their eyes
radiating love for you.
Three long exhales to give this correctly
into this world.
You can slowly open your eyes
again.